// var questions = [
//     {
//         question: "Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
//         correctAnswer: "C.Alerts",
//         choices: ["A.Strings","B.Booleans","C.Alerts","D.Numbers"]
//     },

//     {
//         question: "The condition in an if/else statment is enclosed within___.",
//         correctAnswer: "C.Parentheses",
//         choices: ["A.Quotes","B.Curly brackets","C.Parentheses","D.Square brackets"]
//     },
//     {
//         question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store___.",
//         correctAnswer: "D.All of the above",
//         choices: ["A.Numbers and strings","B.Other arrays","C.Booleans","D.All of the above"]
//     },
//     {
//         question: "String values must be enclosed within___when being assigned to variables",
//         correctAnswer: "C.Quotes",
//         choices: ["A.Comma","B.Curly brackets","C.Quotes","D.Parentheses"]
//     }




// ];

 var questions = [
	{
		question: 'Which is the correct form to output a message to the dev tools?',
		correct: 'console.log()',
		choices: [
			'console.log()',
			'log.console()',
			'displayContent()',
			'showMeWhatThisIs()'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'What element do we use to embed JavaScript into our HTML?',
		correct: '<script>',
		choices: [
			'<script>',
			'<header>',
			'<link>',
			'<javascript>'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'Which primitive data type returns a true or false value?',
		correct: 'boolean',
		choices: [
			'boolean',
			'string',
			'number',
			'ifElse'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'To assign a value to a variable which operator should we use?',
		correct: '=',
		choices: [
			'=',
			'==',
			'===',
			'equals'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'To compare if two values are equal in value and data type which operator should we use?',
		correct: '===',
		choices: [
			'===',
			'==',
			'=',
			'equals'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'Which set of parentheses are used to declare or store values in an array?',
		correct: '[ ] Square',
		choices: [
			'[ ] Square',
			'( ) Round',
			'{ } Curly',
			'< > Angle'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'Which of the following is NOT an expression used to define the parameters of a \'for\' loop?',
		correct: 'Functional',
		choices: [
			'Functional',
			'Declarative',
			'Conditional',
			'Incremental'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'When we want to _____ a declared function we put () after the name.',
		correct: 'Call',
		choices: [
			'Call',
			'Reference',
			'Summon',
			'Trigger'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'If we want a variable to be accessible to any part of our code we declare it _____.',
		correct: 'Globally',
		choices: [
			'Globally',
			'Universally',
			'Locally',
			'Openly'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'Which keyword is NOT used to declare a variable?',
		correct: 'store',
		choices: [
			'store',
			'var',
			'let',
			'const'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'What property of an array returns how many items are stored in it?',
		correct: '.length',
		choices: [
			'.length',
			'.count',
			'.sum',
			'.total'
		]
	},
	{
		question: 'The value of _____ is determined by where it is used and always refers to an object.',
		correct: 'this',
		choices: [
			'this',
			'that',
			'here',
			'aforementioned'
		]
	}
];